Hitesh Pithava

Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India



princebilla4143@gmail.com



7984789723



linkedin.com/in/hitesh-pithava-0560b91b1

Summary

I have a strong foundation in graphic design with 3 years of total experience, 2 of which have been dedicated to creating captivating visual content and materials. My experience encompasses a wide range of design projects, from branding and marketing collateral to web graphics and user interface design.

Experience



Graphic Designer

Zlato Technolabs

Apr 2023 - Present (6 months)

Junior Graphic Designer

Thinking Dots Studio

Feb 2022 - Apr 2023 (1 year 3 months)

Graphic Design Intern

Thinking Dots Studio

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022 (6 months)

Data Operator

Apr 2021 - Nov 2021 (8 months)

Education



Brainz institute

Diploma Multimedia & Animation, Art/Art Studies, General

Feb 2020 - Apr 2022



Gujarat University

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom, Business/Commerce, General 2017 - 2020

Skills

Figma (Software) • Graphic Design • Communication • Strategy • English • Project Management • Adobe Photoshop • CorelDRAW • Adobe Illustrator • Adobe Premiere Pro